As the world man had built was buried in ash, a leader appeared, a man who would later be
known as Raffles I. Raffles and his disciples embarked on a quest to find new light, and
they did. What Raffles found was an unsullied flame, the spark that would kindle an empire.
It won't be long before someone in the Fire Force figures out we're down here in the nether.
You're right, but that's to our advantage. Yona's at the gate. Tell him to be on guard.
We'll assist with preparations and reconnaissance. There's no need for reconnaissance. Our enemy is
the knave with the Adola link. That was close. Hey Shinra, you can read your book after you finish
picking up your toys. One minute. Are you sure? Seems kinda risky. You know bad boys get taken to the nether.
So dumb. Why would I be afraid of the nether?
You don't have to be scared of getting taken to the nether.
have to be scared of getting taken to the nether because your big brother will swoop in to save
you they're in the nether you're sure based on leak's analysis of what clues were left after
the attack on vulcan's workshop we've determined that the evangelist followers are hiding out
underground the holy soul temple tells us the nether is a place far removed from the great
souls light those caverns are both dark and unclean for reasons we just heard from sister iris the
nether which has roots beneath most of tokyo is considered forbidden ground this of course makes
it the perfect place for a band of cultists to set up shop as for what the nether looks like
it's comprised of the now defunct railway tunnels that used to run throughout the city
my understanding was that most of the tunnels collapsed on the day of the great cataclysm
but it's starting to look like more of them survived than one would expect
i looked at what giovanni left behind cross-referenced that with a map of artificial
combustion sites and found where they are
tomorrow we're gonna bust into the secret layer of the bastards who've been burning innocent people
alive we'll knock down all their doors and find the secret of human combustion
expect a full-on battle with all our lives at stake
we're bringing your brother home shinra sir okay let's get ready for tomorrow dismissed
tamaki you have a minute sir are you sure you want to do this
it's so hot where am i
sister iris
earthquake doesn't seem like an especially big one yeah but we're getting more common
in
We'll be right back.
We're finally starting to look like a real company.
Yeah, we are.
We'll be right back.
We're right back.
In order to enter the Nether legally, you have to obtain special permission from the Church.
Most requests are summarily rejected.
In light of our investigation, the Temple has made a reluctant exception, but only for Company 8.
It's like they think whoever goes down there will be corrupted somehow.
The Temple says it's a tainted land, connected to Hell and home to inhuman creatures.
Nobody should go down there.
I can't believe we used to put our trains underground.
So this is it?
The gate to the Nether?
You're freaking out?
So dumb.
Why would I be afraid of the Nether?
Don't be ridiculous.
Hm.
We're really going in there?
Mama would tear me a new one if she knew I was anywhere near here.
You seemed strangely calm, Volk.
Yeah, it's not my favorite place.
But I've gone a few times to check out the water treatment facilities.
Again, not my favorite place.
I don't like this.
Do we really have to go down there?
Stop making such a fuss.
So we go, would you mind if I offered a prayer.
Please do.
That's what we're doing.
So, we're going to get out and get out and get down.
We're really going in there.
You seem strangely calm, Volk.
Yeah, it's not my favorite place.
But I've gone a few times to check out the water treatment facilities.
Again, not my favorite place.
I don't like this.
Do we really have to go down there?
Stop making such a fuss.
Before we go, would you mind if I offered a prayer?
Please do.
Ever do we worship the rising sun.
We beseech thee, grant thy light to the souls of the innocent.
What the hell? Look sharp, everyone.
It opened on its own. It must be Merlin's magic.
Don't be stupid.
This an invitation from the Whiteclad?
Nice. It actually opened. Looks like the electricity still works.
Wait, that was you? Tell us next time!
Vulcan, hey! I don't guess there's another button you can press to turn on a bunch of lights in there!
What does it look like, Captain? See anything?
Nothing ate me.
Didn't realize you were that wound up, Captain.
It sure is dark.
Well, yeah, it is the nether.
Oh, so this is the nether. I can't believe I'm here. Crazy.
Maki, have a light?
Yes, sir. Right here.
Sputter. And flare.
Sputter! Sputter! Sputter! Sputter! Sputter! Sputter! Sputter! Sputter! Sputter!
Sputter! Sputter!
I was hoping for a normal light.
This is the closest place to hell there is. Don't forget that. We'll find the base of the evangelist and the truth about human combustion here. Stay sharp and keep moving.
Yes, sir.
Yona, let's shake things up.
Art is meant to disrupt, and I mean to push art to its limit.
Hold your positions.
Everybody stay close.
Where'd you come from?
Hey, Captain, you here?
Shinra, help! Something's got a hold of me!
Don't let them get me, please!
Hang on, I'm coming!
Don't run off, Shinra! We have to stay close!
Iris, give me your hand.
Right.
At least we knew the two of us are real.
This way! Go!
I found a place where the fog's a lot thinner.
Hurry up!
Oh!
Yo, stop! Don't let the...
Let us up!
No!
Damn it!
I'm only picking up two life forms right now.
Guess everyone but us was lured or dragged away.
Wait a sec.
How do I know if you're the real Captain Obi?
One look at those goggles tells me you're real.
Would an imposter know you well enough to say that?
Sorry, sir.
I made these life-sensing goggles to counteract Mirage's ability.
Didn't occur to me that they'd use fog along with it, as well as living imposters.
This is a sloth snout.
Cool, bro.
Thanks to Mirage and Yona's efforts, we've succeeded in dividing the enemy.
Good.
Send in the exterminator.
Assault.
I shall go as well.
Then again, assault the bloody incendiary around might just wipe out the entire eighth on his own.
Okay, Iris, you know I'm the real one, don't you?
Don't listen to her.
She's lying.
Why are you even struggling to figure this out?
Any way you looking at that weirdo's a fake?
That isn't true.
She's totally the real imposter.
And she's a meanie.
One more thing that proves I'm real, plus I was on your left, remember?
And I have flame ears.
Well, I certainly can't argue with that.
Tote's not fair.
You're trying to fool her by doing something that I can't do.
What a mean trick.
Don't make me cry.
This could be an incredibly clever deception.
Come on!
Why are you acting so dense about this?
She sounds like a grown-ass man!
Nuh-uh.
Ah!
You are the real Tamaki!
Yep.
Now you know for sure, huh?
I'm gonna take out my frustrations with Iris on you, pops!
Hey!
You there!
Niki!
Ah!
Get back here and take what you've got coming!
Hey!
You're the first.
The first on today's long list of targets.
Assault.
The name of the man who will kill you.
I will not hold back.
Well, this bites.
How did I end up all alone down here?
Oh, it's just a woman.
You seem a bit twitchy.
What are you, scared of the dark?
That's the least of your worries down here, little girl.
Well, what a relief.
This place is creepy when you're alone.
I'd almost convinced myself you were ghosts.
What the hell's wrong with this girl?
Has the darkness driven her insane?
Kill her.
You think this is a game?
It's not that.
I'm just glad you're all human.
It means I know how to deal with you.
Prepare to engage.
Hopper at 90 degrees.
Pressure circuits ready.
Release power units.
Pilots to their battle stations.
Maintain formation.
Your name's Flail, right?
I'm told that you and your friends
gave one of my precious little rookies
quite the beating.
Twin hover units, Tecchio, at the ready.
Move out!
Even through your gear,
I can see that you work out.
But you can't actually expect to beat us.
We're all combat professionals.
Yeah?
Can't say I'd have guessed from the looks of you.
How dare you mock us!
So she's a second Jin.
Keep shooting!
Take her down!
Throw those little sparks all you want.
They're nothing to me!
You're an annoying little...
You're an annoying little.
Huuh!
Ah!
ặp!
Uh!
Ah!
Huh!
Uh!
In the evangelist's hallowed name, I grant you death by fire!
I swing it like a mason chain, but I'm in control.
P.D.R. Strike!
Resistance is useless. Just let it crush you.
I don't care how brawny you are, you're still just a woman! You can't hurt me!
Who are you calling?
Gorilla Cyclops!
I better hurry and find the others.
Iris, stay back.
Right.
He's a third Jin too.
Ah, you have decent fire resistance if nothing else.
Are you okay, Tamaki?
I'm fine, get back!
Forgive me, but I have others to deal with.
Besides, enemies or not, I find it distasteful to inflict needless suffering on women.
So I'll make your deaths quick.
Are you sure you want to do this?
It'll be dangerous and you're with Company One.
We'd understand if you bowed out.
Even if it's just because of my suspension, for the time being I'm a member of the Eighth.
Which means I join you on your missions.
Hey, Tamaki.
I hear you're coming with us to the Nether.
If you end up needing to be saved, call for me and I'll come.
Don't forget, I'm a fire soldier too!
My job is to protect people, not be your dumb damsel!
Oh yeah, you are a fire soldier.
I almost forgot.
They gave me this uniform for a reason!
I can do this!
Don't be scared, Iris. I'll protect you!
I am the Assassin from the Abyss.
And you're in my grasp!
You see that I stand before you.
Yet you do not run.
I commend your courage.
But this fight ends now.
Crimson Bullet!
Give me some credit, you arrogant duck!
She dodged it?
You dodged it?
In my grasp...
Get off me!
What do you think you're doing?
I feel so...
Impure!
Lattom...
Lattom!
I won't be done it so easily!
.
How do you like them apples, Kusakabe?
It's plain to see that I'm a badass ass kicker!
Kato! Kato! Kato! Kato!
Lato!
How you like them apples, Kusakabe?
It's plain to see that I'm a badass ass-kicker.
Do you really think that's what he would've gotten out of seeing all that?
What did I say?
Because what I meant is all's well that ends well.
I'm depending on you.
It's pretty dark, so you better stay close.
Okay? Right?
Because I'd like you to podcast about these videos on the screen that I invite you to share with you.
This map also supports many scowns which are pressed vertically or all parties that would also be an klung 1.
Jesus tells me he's right close to someone.
I'll see you next time.